<CATALOG>
    <CD>
        <NAME>adidas Tango adidas México</NAME>
        <DESCRIPTION>Engineered for performance and inspired by our sports heritage, this golf shirt is your faithful partner for honing your short game and climbing the leader board alike. adidas PRIMEKNIT ensure full mobility to match a powerful swing. This product is made with 100% recycled materials. By reusing materials that have already been created, we help to reduce waste and our reliance on finite resources and reduce the footprint of the products we make.</DESCRIPTION>
        <PIC>adidas_Tango.jpg</PIC>
        <TYPE>shirt</TYPE>
    </CD>
    <CD>
        <NAME>ESSENTIALS FRENCH TERRY 3-STRIPES FULL-ZIP HOODIE</NAME>
        <DESCRIPTION>crafted from 100% soft and durable cotton, ensuring both comfort and quality. It features a classic design with a full-zip front, ribbed cuffs, and hem for a snug fit, along with the iconic Adidas logo for a sporty look. Ideal for casual wear or light athletic activities, it combines style with functionality.</DESCRIPTION>
        <PIC>ESSENTIALS_FRENCH_TERRY_3_STRIPES_FULL_ZIP_HOODIE.jpg</PIC>
        <TYPE>shirt</TYPE>
    </CD>
    <CD>
        <NAME>FREELIFT SPORT PRIME HEATHER TEE </NAME>
        <DESCRIPTION>Tight fit
Crewneck
83% polyester (recycled), 17% elastane(spandex)
Mesh back panel
AEROREADY
TECHFIT focuses your muscles' energy
Ultraviolet Protect Factor (UPF)
Low-to-medium compression
Designed for freedom of movement
Colour: Black
Product code: JE6698</DESCRIPTION>
        <PIC>FREELIFT_SPORT_PRIME_HEATHER_TEE.jpg</PIC>
        <TYPE>shirt</TYPE>
    </CD>
    <CD>
        <NAME>Samba Original</NAME>
        <DESCRIPTION>Born on the pitch, the Samba is a timeless icon of street style. This silhouette stays true to its legacy with a tasteful, low-profile, soft leather upper, suede overlays and gum sole, making it a staple in everyone's closet - on and off the pitch.</DESCRIPTION>
        <PIC>samba_original.png</PIC>
        <TYPE>shoes</TYPE>
    </CD>
    <CD>
        <NAME>Adidas Team Issue Sackpack</NAME>
        <DESCRIPTION>Adidas Team Issue Sack Pack is a versatile and durable bag designed for athletes on the go. It features a bold vertical zippered pocket with an interior gusset to keep your gear secure, dual water bottle pockets for hydration, and a spacious main compartment for all your essentials. The sack pack is adorned with the signature Adidas style, making it perfect for daily use or sports activities</DESCRIPTION>
        <PIC>Adidas_Team_Issue_Sackpack.jpg</PIC>
        <TYPE>accessory</TYPE>
    </CD>
    <CD>
        <NAME>Men's Adidas Tiro 21 Training Shorts 2xl Black Athletic Shorts</NAME>
        <DESCRIPTION>This is a pair of black, tight-fitting athletic shorts made from 88% recycled polyester and 12% elastane (spandex), featuring an elastic waist, moisture-absorbing AEROREADY technology, a 3D sculpted, mesh-lined pouch, designed for motion, and made with single jersey fabric, with the product code HJ9921.</DESCRIPTION>
        <PIC>Tiro.jpg</PIC>
        <TYPE>shorts</TYPE>
    </CD>
    <CD>
        <NAME>tango Pants</NAME>
        <DESCRIPTION>This is a pair of medium grey heather shorts in a regular fit, made from 100% Better Cotton, featuring a drawcord on an elastic waist, side pockets, and an inseam measuring 17.75 cm, with the product code IC9437.</DESCRIPTION>
        <PIC>tango_pants.jpg</PIC>
        <TYPE>shorts</TYPE>
    </CD>
    <CD>
        <NAME>adidas skateboarding whiteblackgum adicourt stripes</NAME>
        <DESCRIPTION>The Adidas Skateboarding Adicourt Stripes in white/black/gum is a sleek and durable skate shoe that offers both style and functionality. It features a crisp white leather upper with black stripes and a gum sole for excellent grip and board feel. The padded collar and cushioned footbed provide comfort and support for skateboarding or casual wear, while the classic silhouette ensures these shoes will look great on and off the board.</DESCRIPTION>
        <PIC>adidas_skateboarding_whiteblackgum_adicourt_stripes.jpg</PIC>
        <TYPE>shoes</TYPE>
    </CD>
    <CD>
        <NAME>Adidas Blue Suede Shoes</NAME>
        <DESCRIPTION>Adidas Blue Suede Shoes combine classic style with modern comfort. They feature a rich blue suede upper for a luxurious look and feel, with the iconic three stripes in contrasting white. The low-top design ensures versatility and ease of movement, while the cushioned insole provides support for all-day wear. Perfect for adding a pop of color to any outfit, these shoes are a stylish choice for both casual and athletic occasions.</DESCRIPTION>
        <PIC>adidas_blue_suede_shoes.jpg</PIC>
        <TYPE>shoes</TYPE>
    </CD>
    <CD>
        <NAME>Black Adidas Baseball Cap</NAME>
        <DESCRIPTION>100% recycled polyester plain weave
Soft feel
Sunny-day hat
Medium curve crown and brim
Plain weave
Colour: Black / Sharp Blue / White
Product code: FN5922</DESCRIPTION>
        <PIC>adidas_black_cap.jpg</PIC>
        <TYPE>accessory</TYPE>
    </CD>
    <CD>
        <NAME>Techfit Compression Training Tee Black Mens Training T Shirts</NAME>
        <DESCRIPTION>The compression fit hugs your muscles, directing your energy into powerful, accelerated moves that improve your endurance. Mesh ventilation releases excess heat, so you can dig deep. Your training partner? It's the shirt you never notice.This product is made with at least 70% recycled materials. By reusing materials that have already been created, we help to reduce waste and our reliance on finite resources and reduce the footprint of the products we make.</DESCRIPTION>
        <PIC>Techfit_Compression_Training_Tee_Black_Mens_Training_T_Shirts.jpg</PIC>
        <TYPE>shirt</TYPE>
    </CD>
    <CD>
        <NAME>BLACK ALPHASKIN SPORT SHORT TIGHTS</NAME>
        <DESCRIPTION>100% polyester piqué,climalite fabric sweeps sweat away from your skin,Drawcord on elastic waist,3-Stripes down sides,Embroidered adidas brandmark,18.5 cm inseam (size 50),Regular Fit,Colour: Dark Blue / White,Product code: BK4765</DESCRIPTION>
        <PIC>BLACK_ALPHASKIN_SPORT_SHORT_TIGHTS.jpg</PIC>
        <TYPE>shorts</TYPE>
    </CD>
    <CD>
        <NAME>SLEEK 3-STRIPES SHORTS MADE WITH RECYCLED MATERIALS</NAME>
        <DESCRIPTION>Iconic '80s style makes a comeback. Built in classic doubleknit fabric, these adidas shorts stand out with embossed 3-Stripes for an understated retro vibe. The easy-wearing regular fit keeps things casual and comfortable, whether you're enjoying downtime at home or stepping out for the day. This product is made with 100% recycled materials. By reusing materials that have already been created, we help to reduce waste and our reliance on finite resources and reduce the footprint of the products we make.</DESCRIPTION>
        <PIC>SLEEK_3STRIPES_SHORTS_MADE_WITH_RECYCLED_MATERIALS.png</PIC>
        <TYPE>shorts</TYPE>
    </CD>
    <CD>
        <NAME>THESE GO-TO SHORTS ARE MADE IN PART WITH RECYCLED MATERIALS</NAME>
        <DESCRIPTION>These shorts are a modern take on an adidas original. Reinvented for today yet inspired by iconic archives, they're a fresh remix and a classic style staple. Made with a lightweight tricot fabric, they let you move freely while paying homage to the brand that started it all. Side pockets add convenience while a drawcord on the elastic waist supplies a customised fit. This product is made with at least 70% recycled materials. By reusing materials that have already been created, we help to reduce waste and our reliance on finite resources and reduce the footprint of the products we make.</DESCRIPTION>
        <PIC>THESE_GOTO_SHORTS_ARE_MADE_IN_PART_WITH_RECYCLED_MATERIALS.png</PIC>
        <TYPE>shorts</TYPE>
    </CD>
</CATALOG>
